How are you doing my name is Lars Eric Robinson I'm with LarsEr Arts All Around Art-tainment. I'm a freelance illustrator.
Today I'm going to talk about something that's you probably want to know about if you are painting and you are working and you are having clothes and you don't want to get anything on it.
As you can tell right here I have a paint stain right here on my pants.
You take mineral spirits, the same medium thinner that you are using for your oils.
You dab it on both sides, you put it on there.
Once you notice it dropped on there, you let it soak.
Then maybe when you are done at the end of the day, you could take this same stain that you have on there, and you put your dish washing soap on both sides and rub it in.
And then wash it, just like a normal clothes.
It should definitely be able to come out, so just remember you use this paint thinner that you had, that you were painting with and just dab it on there, you can scrub it a little bit and then when you are done just wash it like a normal clothes.
It should come straight off, there's other cleaning mediums out there that you can look for too, they have a powder form that should be able to take your paint right off.
Hope that explains to you what we go through as artists to try to get our paint off our clothes.
Thank you so much.